Wadsworth Family Papers 1790-1950
Wadsworth Family Papers
- Persons Who Worked for the Wadsworths as Farm or Day Laborers, 1831-1842; 5 ledgers
  - Farm Accounts and Hired Hands, 1834-1838:; A (Box AW1)
    List at Beginning of Book:
    Babcock, Elihu
    Clement, Henry
    Davis, James
    Davis, John
    Eldrid, William
    Eldridge, Erastus
    Emons, George
    Evringham, S
    Gaston, William
    Grant, A A
    Henry, Andrew
    Joslin, Luke
    Mack, Solomon
    McLeary, James
    Osman, William
    Rathbone, Harrison
    Reinhold
    Scribner, Albert
    Siles, George
    Simmons, Henry
    Tanner, John A
    Tarbox, Jonathon
    Teneyck, Lemuel
    Weaver, Solomon
    Webster, Horace
    Webster, Simon
    Willard, A
    Willard, Frederick
  - Farm Accounts and Hired Hands, 1838:; A (Box AW1)
    In Small Insert:
    Baker, Frederick
    Bowman, George
    Butler, Francis
    Clark, Henry
    Clark, James
    Clark, Robert
    Davis, Henry
    Davis, Thomas
    Dean, John
    Eanos, J B
    Fink, John
    Fisk, John
    Foster, Hosen
    French, Lewis D
    Fuse, William
    Gaston, John
    Gear, David
    Graham, Andrew
    Grisby, Jeorge
    Hunt, Jacob
    Jones, Zalmon
    Leary, James
    Lockwood, Lewis
    Loveland, Norman
    Maise, Daniel
    Minor, John
    Morse, Joseph
    Parsons, Luke
    Robinson, Saunton
    Rogers, John
    Rounds, Levi
    Rugg, Lyman
    Sanders, John
    Saxton, Samuel
    Seaman, Albert
    Shepard, Cheney
    Shouts, Christian
    Smith, Joseph
    Spencer, William
    Truman, Stank
    Starkweather, Isaac
    Stiles, Simon
    Stratton, Hiram
    Sweet, James
    Sweet, John
    Swift, Eben
    Swift, hineas
    Swift, Samuel
    Teal, Henry
    Thomston, Ziba
    Wakeley, Samuel
    Willard, Alvarius
    Wilson, Jame
  - Farm Accounts and Hired Hands, 1839-1840:; B (Box AW1)
    Adams, Thomas
    Balch, C C
    Barry, John
    Burdick, Sarah
    Carsons, Alexander
    Cooling, Charles
    Derby, Abgeline
    Garvin, Lewis
    Gill, Robert
    Haling, Abraham
    Hawley, Josiah
    Hill, Chloe
    Kriger, H
    Kriger, J
    Landon, Thomas
    McAllister, Robert
    McDermott, Colin
    Munson, William
    Page, John
    Pierce, Charles
    Pierce, Levi
    Reynolds, Henry
    Robinson, John
    Swift, Ph
    Wheeler, Daniel
  - Farm Accounts and Hired Hands, 1841-1842:; C (Box AW1)
    John Allen
    Lewis Backer
    John Barry
    Anthony Barton
    William Benton
    Thomas Boothman
    Lewis Bower
    John Brown
    Aaron Chase
    Chester Comstock
    Charles Cooling
    William Delude
    John Divine
    Sally Farnham
    Michael Galvin
    G. Gilbert
    G. Gillies
    Peter Glaser
    Peter Glass
    James Gregg
    Jacob Haly
    John Haly
    J. Harback
    John Harback
    William Kennedy
    John Kirkby
    August Lander
    Charles Lewis
    Henry Ling
    Michael Ling
    Daniel Luckenbill
    Daniel Manning
    Clovis Mather
    Elizabeth McFall
    Thomas McFall
    L. McWitty
    Phillip Monte
    John Morrison
    .. Munger
    B. Nevil
    John Rahorn
    Adam Reitsel
    William Sheen
    John Thanisch
    Ephraim Willard
  - Farm Accounts and Hired Hands, April, 12 1841-June 9, 1841:; D (Box unwrapped)
    Bacher, Lewis
    Baker, William
    Barton, Anthony
    Benton, William
    Bishop, Henry
    Delude, William
    Devine, John
    Dorshit, John
    Glaser, Peter
    Green
    Hawley, J.
    Hopkins, Charles
    Keersch
    Kennedy, William
    Kirkby, John
    Manning, Daniel
    McCleary, James
    Miner, John
    Murry, William
    Putney, William
    Shuttles, Harrison
    Sloan, John
    Sloucum, Henry
    South, Daniel
    Wallace, John Jacob
Selective Name and Subject Index
Adair, Cornelia Wadsworth Daughter of General James S., Letters (1) December 23, 1909 Wadsworth, William Austin Wadsworth, James S. Biography information for Author. Box LWAW1 F 1 Shelf 26
Adams, Brooks (1848-1927) Author and Lawyer, Letters (16) 1879-86 Wadsworth,William Austin Estate business Box LWAW1 F 2 Shelf 26
Adams, Charles Francis III (1866-1954 Secretary of Navy Letters from (2) 1929 Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. Ammo Depot Box J112D F 1 Sh 59
Adams, John Quincy (1767-1848) 6th US President, Letters Patent (1) 1826 Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Michigan lands Box CM2 Shelf 14
Agnew, Cornelius Rea (1830-1888) Physician Letters from (2) 1881 Wadsworth,William Austin Personal Box LWAW1 F 3 Shelf 26
Albany Advertiser, Albany NY Newspaper 1816-1817 scattered issues Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Advertising for goods and services; News Volume 2 Shelf 40
Albany Gazette, Albany NY Newspaper 1795-1828 scattered issues. Wadsworth, James (1768-1844) Advertising for goods and services; News. Volume 2 Shelf 40
Albany Register, Albany NY Newspaper 1799-1820 scattered issues. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Advertising for goods and services; News. Volume 2 Shelf 40
Alexander, Henry Martin (d. 1899) Lawyer Letters 1882-1883 Wadsworth,William Austin Estate business. Box LWAW1 F 4 Shelf 26
Allen, Henry Justin (1868-1950) Newspaper publisher Letter September 14, 1906. Wadsworth,William Austin Hunt Club. Box LWAW1 F 5 Shelf 26
Allen, Hezekiah (1821-87) Financial agent 44 yrs, Letters to and from (50+) 1853-1872. Wadsworth,Emmeline Austin Estate business for Emmeline, Craig W., Wm. Austin. Box LMisc1 Shelf 24
Allen, Hezekiah (1821-87) Financial agent 44 yrs Letters to (50+) 1850+ Wadsworth family Family business in Geneseo. Boxes L 7-15;18+ Sh 16+
Alvord, Augustus; Orlow Beeber Caledonia farmers Lease 1845 Wadsworth,William Wolcott Caledonia land. Box C2 Fold. 16 Shelf 9
Ambrose, Nathaniel Henrietta settler Bill of Sale 2 copies 1833 Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Henrietta land. Box C1 Fold. 5 Shelf 9
American Economist Issue of July 2 1926 Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. Wadsworth, James W., Jr Special Issue of magazine. Box J112E F 26 Sh 59
American Hotel Buffalo, NY Bill May 2, 1841 Wadsworth,William Wolcott Hotel lodging and food: Example of vouchers' scope. Box V1 Hotels Shelf 27
American Hotel, Auburn, NY Bill February 3, 1838 Wadsworth,William Wolcott Hotel lodging and food: Example of vouchers' scope. Box V1 Hotels Shelf 27
Amory, A S Nahant MA Letters from (2) Wadsworth,Emmeline Austin Personal Box LEAW1 F 5 Shelf 23
Anderson, J. W. Ohio settler Letters to (8) 1836-1842 Wadsworth,James S (1807-1864) Ohio lands Box LBk 1 Sh 27-Indexed
Angel, Benjamin Franklin (1815-1894) Lawyer and diplomat Letters from (2) 1842 Wadsworth, James S. (1807-1864) Personal Index in print and on microfilm Location: Lib Congress Microfilm
Appleton, Thomas Gold, (b. 1812) Boston friend and author Letters 1830-1850 Wadsworth,William Wolcott Friends. Use calendars in-Location: Box L1-L4 Shelf 15
Association Against the Prohibition Amendment Statistics (2) [1927] Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. Prohibition's cost to Government, etc. Box J112J F 9 Shelf 60
Astor House, New York City Bills (4) 1939-1841 Wadsworth,William Wolcott Hotel lodging and food: Example of vouchers' scope. Box V1 Hotels Shelf 27
Austin Family of Boston, Genealogy-select pages 1951 Wadsworth,Emmeline Austin Austin family; descend. Richard Austin of Charleston. File Cab. 1 Drawer 1
Austin, Charles, Mother's relative, Letters from (4) 1871-1895 Wadsworth,William Austin Japan. Box LWAW1 F 6 Shelf 26
Austin, Edward (1803-1899) Mother's brother, Letters from (80) 1869-1895 Wadsworth,William Austin Personal and Business. He was active in East India trade Box LWAW1 Fs 7-12 Sh 26
Avon township, Maps 19th century Wadsworth,James; Wadsworth,James S Avon settlers and land owners. Map File, Both sets
Avon, Genesee and Mt. Morris Railroad Account Books (2) 1860-1898 Wadsworth, James Samuel Railroad accounts; Ledger and Journal. Shelf 51
Backus, E F, Merchant, 67 State St., Albany, Letters to (5) September 13, 1815+. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Wallpaper order; Books and magazine orders. Bk 61 Sh 27 use index
Bacon, Selden (1861-1946) Connecticut lawyer Proposal for Amendment Wadsworth, James Wolcott, Jr. Constitutional Amendments. Box J112E F 6 Shelf 59
Bailey, Marcellus Attorney and Patent Solicitor, Washington DC Letters from (17) 1878-1879 Wadsworth,Herbert (1851-1927) Patent on anvil. Box LHW1 Shelf 24
Baird, Frank Burkett Builder of Peace Bridge, and others Letters to and from (8) 1927 Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr Peace Bridge Dedication Box J112E F 25 Sh 59
Ball, Thompkins and Black New York City clothiers Bill April 16, 1840 Wadsworth,William Wolcott Tailoring, buttons: Example of vouchers' scope. Box V1 Clothing Sh 27
Bancroft, George (1800-1891) Historian;Sec of Navy Letters from (5) 1879-1884 Wadsworth,Emmeline Austin Friends in Boston and family. Box LEAW1 Shelf 23
Barbor and Avery Hardware store Bill [1838-40] Wadsworth,William Wolcott Carpenters' tools. Example of vouchers' scope. Box V1 Hardware Ch 27
Baring Brothers Company, London, England, Letter 1837 Wadsworth,William Wolcott
Agent: -(Book 58)
Wheat rust effects supply. Box LBk1 P 85 Shelf 27
Barrett, F W Wadsworth NY, Letter October 24, 1895 Wadsworth,William Austin Sheep: Ram for sale. Box LWAW1 F 13 Shelf 26
Barringer, Daniel Moreau (1860-1929) Mining Engineer Letters (5) 1901-1902 Wadsworth:\ William Austin Hunting in the Sierra Madra. Box LWAW1 F 14 Shelf 26
Barrymore, Elizabeth Wadsworth, Lady (b1848) Daughter Account Book/Journal LB 1907-1922 Wadsworth,James S. (1807-1864) Estate records of wife of Arthur Smith-Barrymore. Box J87 Shelf 50
Barrymore, Sybil Daughter of Lady Barrymore (?) Letter Wadsworth,William Austin Personal Box LWAW1 F 15 Shelf 26
Belmont, August (1853-1924) Banker Letters (3) 1909 Wadsworth,William Austin Hunt Box LWAW1 F 16 Shelf 26
Bennett, Alva Geneseo High School Bill June 12, 1838 Wadsworth,William Wolcott
Agent: -Hammatt
School tuition for 3: Example of vouchers' scope. Box V1 Education Sh 27
Biddle, Nicholas (1786-1844) 2nd US National Bank Letter 7/21/1838 Wadsworth,James S. (1807-1864) Business matters Index in print and on microfilm Location: Lib Congress Microfilm
Bigelow Head of School in Canandaigua Letter August 12, 1816 Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Wadsworth, Harriet; Her education. Bk 61 P 140 Shelf 27
Bigelow, D J Boston Letters (2) Wadsworth,William Austin Bigelow, Wm. Sturgis; Conversation Club of friends. Box LWAW1 Fs 17-18 Sh26
Bigelow, James (1787-1879) Boston Letter September 6, 1870 Wadsworth,Emmeline Austin Personal Box LEAW1 Shelf 23
Bigelow, William Sturgis MD Author; Buddhism; Signed "Silene" Letters 1870+ Wadsworth,William Austin Japan and other travels Interesting pencil sketches. Box LWAW1 Fs 19-25 Sh26
Blair, Francis Preston (1821-1875) Politician; Reporter Letter 6/28/1848 Wadsworth,James S. (1807-1864) Personal Index in print and on microfilm Location: Lib Congress Microfilm
Bloomfield, John, Norfolk, England, Letter December 11, 1836. Wadsworth,William Wolcott
Agent: -(Book 58)
England trip; English laborers he brought to Geneseo. Box LBk 1 P 75 Sh 27
Bond, Chauncey Assistant to Agent Wm. Cushing, Letter February 1836. Wadsworth,William Wolcott
Agent: -(Book 58)
Cattle: Comparison of stock in New York and Ohio. Box LBk 1 P 34 Shelf 27
Bond, William M Agent and resident of Mt. Morris, Letters to (18) 1864 Wadsworth family Family business Box 10 Shelf 16
Botsford, Samuel B, Jackson Health Resort, Dansville. Letter 1927 Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. Hospital proposal for Dansville; Jackson Health Resort. Box J112E F 17 Sh 59
Bowditch, Charles P Boston Agent and Attorney Letter 2/16/1871 Wadsworth,Emmeline Austin Episcopal Society's problems re card playing. Box LMisc1 F 15 Sh 24
Bowditch, Charles P Boston Agent and Attorney Letter 1853-1872 Wadsworth,Emmeline Austin Estate business for Emmeline, Craig W., Wm. Austin. Box LMisc1 Shelf 24
Bowditch, Charles P Boston Agent and Attorney Letters to (50+) 1865-1892 Wadsworth family Family business Boxes L 11-15 Sh 16-17
Bowditch, Charles P Boston Agent and Attorney Letters to Ed. Austin 1869-1872 Wadsworth,Emmeline Austin Family business Box LMisc1 Shelf 24
Bowditch, Charles P Boston Agent and Attorney Letters from 11/21/1871 Wadsworth,Emmeline Austin Farm property values in New York State and Ohio. Box LMisc1 F 15 Sh 24
Bowditch, Charles P Boston Agent and Attorney Letters from (2) 2/3 and 11/22/1871 Wadsworth,Emmeline Austin Homestead sale; advice about leaving Geneseo. Box LMisc1 F 15 Sh 24
Bowditch, Charles P Boston Agent and Attorney Letters from (2) 2/4 and 3/4/1869 Wadsworth,Emmeline Austin Normal school location. Box LMisc1 F 13 Sh 24
Bowditch, Charles P Boston Agent and Attorney Plans in letter from June 18, 1869 Wadsworth,Emmeline Austin Stained glass Rose Window for st. Michael's Church. Box LMisc1 F 8 Sh 24
Bowditch, Charles P Boston Agent and Attorney Letters from 11/16/1872 Wadsworth,Emmeline Austin Wadsworth Estate's control surrendered to Allen. Box LMisc1 F 16 Sh 24
Bowne, Robert Pulteney agency in Livonia Letters to (26) October 12, 1815+ Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Pulteney Estate land accounts; Settlers' problems. Bk 61 Sh 27 use index
Bowne, Robert Pulteney agency in Livonia Letters to August 15, 1816. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Weather, 1816 "year of 1800 and froze to death"; crops. Bk 61 P 142 Shelf 27
Brainard, D (1856-1946) US Army Commissary Letters from (3) 1907-12 Wadsworth,William Austin Hunt Box LWAW1 F 26 Shelf 26
Breck, Joseph and Company, Boston, MA, Bill March 5, 1837 Wadsworth,William Wolcott Garden tools: Example of vouchers' scope. Box V1 Gardens Shelf 27
Brimmer and Co. Boston, buyer of Wadsworth wool and flour Letter to October 14, 1834 Wadsworth,William Wolcott
Agent: -(Book 58)
Flour order held up because mill streams were low. Box LBk 1 p 2 Sh 27
Brimmer, Harriet Wadsworth, Wife of Martin Brimmer and sister Letters from (11) 1828-1831 Wadsworth,James S.; Wadsworth,William W. Personal Index in print and on microfilm Location: Lib Congress Microfilm
Brimmer, Marianne Letter from Wadsworth,William Austin Thank you for help; asking for more advice. Box LWAW1 F 28 Shelf 26
Brimmer, Martin Boston Attorney; Husband of Harriet Letters from (23) 1828-1844 Wadsworth,Daniel; Wadsworth,James S
Agent: William W.
Family and Business Index in print and on microfilm Location: Lib Congress Microfilm
Brimmer, Martin Boston Attorney; Husband of Harriet Letters from (7) 1878-1886 Wadsworth,William Austin Family and Business. Box LWAW1 F 29 Shelf 26
Brimmer, Martin Husband of Harriet Letters to (4) 1834-1835 Wadsworth,William Wolcott
Agent: -(Book 58)
Family and Business. Box LBk 1 Sh 27-indexed
Britton, Edward Elms (1864-1925) Brooklyn NY Editor Letter from October 21, 1901 Wadsworth,William Austin National Guard. Box LWAW1 F 30 Shelf 26
Brodie, William A (1841-1917) Homestead Office Letters; vouchers (50+) 1872-1917. Wadsworth,James S; Wharton, Craig Estate business for Emmeline, Craig W., James S. etc. Box LMisc2 Shelf 24
Brodie, William A (1841-1917) Homestead Office Letters to (50+) 1880-1917 Wadsworth family Family business Boxes L 18+ Shelves 17+
Bronson, F, Lt. Letter to November 31, 1836. Wadsworth,James S (1807-1864) Subjects: Ohio, Michigan, Indiana lands; U.S. investment in. Box LBk 1 P 7 Sh 27
Bronson, Frederick Greenfield Hill CT Letter from September 10, 1887. Wadsworth,William Austin Personal. Box LWAWl F 31 Shelf 26
Brooklyn Botanical Garden Calendar reproductions 1979-1980 Wadsworth,Martha Blow Wild flowers of the Genesee Valley in watercolors. Map file Drawer 20
Brooks, Phillips (1835-1893) Episcopal Bishop Letter from February 25, 1884 Wadsworth,Emmeline Austin Thank you for gift of a religious picture. Box LEAWl Shelf 23
Brow, Margaret D Letter from Wadsworth,William Austin Library: Advice about purchase of "Isis Observed." Box LWAWl F 32 Shelf 26
Bruen, Mary A Walnut Street, Boston MA, Letters from (3) Wadsworth,Emmeline Austin Personal; Mrs. Astor's visit. Box LEAWl F 11 Shelf 23
Budlong, Milton Caledonia farmer Lease January 1846 Wadsworth,William Wolcott Ayrault Farm, Caledonia Box C2 Fold. Shelf 9
Buffalo Creek Reservation Map 19th century Wadsworth, James (1768-1844) Indian lands.
See Also Indian Treaty of 1838.
Map File #2
Bull, John B. and James, New York City, Bill April 18, 1838 Wadsworth,William Wolcott Cane, Example of vouchers' scope. Box V1 Clothing Sh 27
Burden, James (1871-1932) Iron Manufacturer Letters from (2) 1881 Wadsworth,William Austin Regrets, Invitation to Hunt. Box LWAW1 F 33 Shelf 26
Burnett, William (d. 1826) Brig. General of Militia Letter to November 14, 1815. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Note due. Bk 61 P 19 Shelf 27
Bush, S D Boston Cotton Buyer Letter from September 27, 1895 Wadsworth,William Austin Regrets, Invitation to Hunt. Box LWAW1 F 34 Shelf 26
Bushnell, N Geneseo resident, and others Letter to December 9, 1818 Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Church Pew rents; 2nd Presbyterian Church, Geneseo. Bk 61 P 460 Shelf 27
Butler, Nicholas Murray (1862-1947) Pres. Columbia Univ., Letter from 1934 Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. Politics. Box J112D F 18 Sh 59
Caledonia township Map 19th century Wadsworth,James S (1807-1864) Caledonia settlers before LeRoy was split off. Map File #1 Main set
Caneadea Reservation Map 19th century Wadsworth,James S (1807-1864) Indian lands. Map File #1 Main set
Canadian Colonial Airways List of board Members 6/20/1928 Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. Airlines. Box J112E F 1
Canal Commissioners of New York State Letter to ca 1837 Wadsworth,James S (1807-1864) Erie Canal feeder lands problems on Oak Orchard Creek. Box LBk 1 P 8 Sh 27
Canaseraga Creek Documents (6 folders) 1908-1913 Wadsworth,William Austin Canaseraga Creek flood control project. File Cab. I, Drawer 2
Canawaugus canal basin, Genesee Valley Canal, Plans (1 folder) 1845 Wadsworth,James; William Wolcott Genesee Valley Canal basin and warehouse specification File Cab. I, Drawer 2
Canawaugus Reservation Map 19th century Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Indian lands Map File #2
Cannon, D G B Burlington VT Letter from Wadsworth,William Austin Regrets, Invitation to Hunt. Box LWAW1 F 35 Shelf 26
Capron, Seth MD, Utica NY Woolen cloth manufacture Letters to (3) 1819 Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Wool; See Also Subject Heading "Sheep." Bk 61 Sh 27 use index
Carroll, Charles (1737-1832) Groveland settler Letter to 4/17/1821 by Wm. Fitzhugh Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. Politics in Western New York. Box J112D F 5 Sh 59
Cary, Charles MD (1893-1931) Buffalo Med School Letters from (2) 1881-1882 Wadsworth,William Austin Regrets, Invitation to Hunt. Box LWAW1 F 36 Shelf 26
Cary, Emlyn Ramsey Wife of Dr. Charles Letters from 1887-1895 Wadsworth,William Austin Regrets, Invitation to Hunt and Personal. Box LWAW1 F 37 Shelf 26
Cary, Thomas, "Tom" Banker in Batavia, New York Letters from (7) 1882-1885 Wadsworth,William Austin Hunt Box LWAW1 F 38 Shelf 26
Cass, Lewis (1782-1866) Diplomat and statesman, Letter from 8/4/1843. Wadsworth: James S. (1807-1864) Politics. Index in print and on microfilm Location: Lib Congress Microfilm
Catteraugus Reservation Map 19th century Wadsworth, James S (1807-1864) Indian lands. Map File #1 Main set
Chandler, Dorothy, "Cooty" Piffard resident Letter from Wadsworth,William Austin Hunt Box LWAW1 F 39 Shelf 26
Chanler, Charles Winthrop, "Winty," 3rd Master of the Hunt, Letters from (2 Folders) 1893+ Wadsworth,William Austin
Agent- 1 to Teddy Roosevelt
Hunt; World War I; Spanish American War. Box LWAW1 Fs 40-41 Sh26
Chase, L D, Pastor Methodist Episcopal Church, Avon, Letter from January 17, 1877. Wadsworth,Emmeline Austin Church donation, Thank You. Box LEAW1 F 12 Shelf 23
Chili township Map 19th century Wadsworth, James S (1807-1864) Chili settlers and land owners. Map File #1 Main Set
Church Family, Angelica Allegany County NY and elsewhere Letters from (3) 1865-1887 Wadsworth,William Austin State Fair; Personal. Box LWAW1 Fs 43-45 Sh26
Church Family, Angelica Allegany County NY and elsewhere Letters from 1828-1840. Wadsworth, Daniel and James S. Western NY and Personal. Index in print and on microfilm Location: Lib Congress Microfilm
Church, Charles Ogden settler and first merchant, Bill of Sale 1847 Wadsworth,William Wolcott Ogden land. Box C1 Fold. 6 Shelf 9
City Hotel, Hartford CT, Bills (4) February 12, 1838 Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Hotel lodging and food: Example of vouchers' scope. Box V1 Hotels Shelf 27
Clay, Henry (1777-1852) Statesman Letter from 9/12/1842 Wadsworth,James S. (1807-1864) Personal. Index in print and on microfilm Lib Congress Microfilm
Clearwater, Alphonso T (1848-1933) Judge, and others, Letters to and from (16) 1927 Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. Am. Revolution Sesqui. Saratoga; Bennington; Kingston. Box J112E F 24 Sh 59
Cleveland, Sarah R and daughter Lily, Nutwood, Letters from (2) Wadsworth,Emmeline Austin Personal; Memories of Europe. Box LEAW1 F 13 Shelf 23
Coleman, William A New York City importer Bill February 12, 1839 Wadsworth,William Wolcott Books; Bristol board. Example of vouchers' scope. Box Vi Books Shelf 27
Comstock, Anna Botsford (1854-1930) Cornell Scientist Letters from (20) 1890-1912 Wadsworth,William Austin Camping, Adirondaks and Cayuga Lake; Signed "Grandma." Box LWAWl Fs 48-50 Sh26
Comstock, Lee Geneseo cattle drover Letters from 1840-1843 Wadsworth,William Wolcott Cattle drives to New York and New Jersey described. Box L3 See Calendars
Comstock, Lee Geneseo cattle drover Bill of sale October 12, 1840 Wadsworth,William Wolcott Cattle sold. Box Vi Comstock Sh 27
Cone, Joseph (1805-1884) Geneseo NY, Letter from April 27, 1879. Wadsworth,Herbert (1851-1927) Sugar Beet culture. Box LHWa Shelf 24
Connecticut Courant, Hartford CT Newspaper 1799-1828 scattered issues. Wadsworth,James (1768-i844) Advertising for goods and services; News. Volume 1 Shelf 40
Connecticut Courant Hartford CT Newspaper November 2, 1812. Wadsworth,William War of 1812; Battle of Queenston as reported by Wedworth Map file Drawer 20
Coolidge, Calvin (1872-1933) 30th President of US, Letters from (2) 1927 and 1931. Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. Politics. Box J112D F 2 Sh 59
Corbin, W Lygon, Letters from (7) 1830. Wadsworth, James S. (1807-1864) Personal. Index in print and on microfilm Lib Congress Microfilm
Corp, Samuel, New York City, Letters to (3) 1818. Wadsworth, James (1768-1844) Debt; Income from farming, etc. Bk 61 Sh 27 use index
Corti, L Art dealer in Europe, Letters from (4) 1873-1876. Wadsworth, Emmeline Austin Art works. Box LEAW1 F 15 Shelf 23
Corti, L Art dealer in Europe, Letter from February 24, 1876. Wadsworth,William Austin Art works; china. Box LWAW1 F 52 Shelf 26
Countryman, Herbert I Editor Silver Springs NY "Signal" Letter from April 7, 1898 Wadsworth,William Austin Politics. Box LWAW1 F 53 Shelf 26
Critz, John of Elba, and Moses True, Oakfield Agent Lease 1841. Wadsworth,William Wolcott Elba land. Box C1 Fold. 27 Shelf 9
Croswell, Edwin (1797-1871) Editor Albany Argus Letter from 10/25/1842 Wadsworth,James S. (1807-1864) Public affairs. Index in print and on microfilm Lib Congress Microfilm
Curtis, Louis Banker and friend in Boston Letters from (12) 1862-1872 Wadsworth,William Austin Personal; Study in Europe. Box LWAW1 F 54 Shelf 26
Cushing, William, Estate Manager and Bank director Letters to (50+) 1847-1854 Wadsworth family Family business and Estate management. Boxes L 4-7 Sh 15-16
Cushing, William Geneseo Estate Manager and Bank director Letter to January 16, 1845 Wadsworth,William Wolcott
Agent-(Book 58)
Sheep and livestock; Division of stock on the estate. Box LBk1 P 168 Shelf 27
Davis, Hiram, Perrysburg OH, Letter to July 25, 1839 Wadsworth,William Wolcott
Agent-(Book 58)
Wheat rust. Box LBk1 P 117 Shelf 27
Dean, Daniel, Michigan, Letter to January 22, 1842 Wadsworth,James S (1807-1864) Michigan lands. Box LBk 1 P 70 Sh 27
Deering, Charles (1852-1927) International Harvester, Letters from (4 folds) 1871-1902 Wadsworth,William Austin Personal; his escapades Box LWAW2 Fs 4-7 Sh 26